A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential records, Foreign Affairs and National Security, Series 19 FA385
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Captain Howe Memoranda of Conversation, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 99)
- Memoranda of Conversation, August 1974-April 1975 (Box 5, Folder 100)
- Memoranda of Conversation, May-December 1975 (Box 5, Folder 100.1)
- Requests for Meeting with the Vice President, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 101)
- Requests for Meetings with the Vice President, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 101.1)
- Requests for Meeting with the Vice President, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 102)
- Murphy Commission, 1973-1977
  - Chron File #1, January-March 1975 (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - Chron File #2, March-April 1975 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Chron File #3, April 1975 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Chron File #4, April-May 1975 (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - Chron File #5, May 1975 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - Chron File #6, May-June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - Chron File #7, June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - Chron File #8, June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - Chron File #9, June-August 1975 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - Press File, June-July 1975 (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - Drafts - National Security, March-April 1975 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Drafts - Intelligence, March-June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Drafts - Economics, April 1975 (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - Drafts - Diplomacy, March-June 1975 (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - Congressional Survey Report, March 1975 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Files - Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Files - Congressional Chapter, 1974-1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Files - Congressional Chapter, 1974-1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 6, Folder 119.1)
  - NAR Participation, January 5, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - NAR Notes, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 121)
- NOT USED (Box 6, Folder 122-192)
- Intelligence Review and Reorganization, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 193)
- Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 194)
- President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board (PFIAB), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 195)
- Economic Intelligence Weekly, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 196)
- Pertinent National Security Developments, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 197)
- Pertinent National Security Developments, January-June 1976 (Box 7, Folder 198)
- Pertinent National Security Developments, January-June 1975 (Box 7, Folder 199)
- Pertinent National Security Developments, July-December 1975 (Box 7, Folder 199.1)
- Pertinent National Security Developments, July-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 200)
- National Security Study Memoranda, 1969-1976 (Box 7, Folder 201)
- Dr. Edward Teller, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 202)
- National Security Council General Items, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 203)
- Civil Defense, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 204)
- National Security Decision Memoranda, 1969, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 205)
- Defense General Items, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 206)
- Defense General Items, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 206.1)
- Strategic, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 207)
- Cruise Missiles, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 208)
- Mutual Balanced Force Reduction (MBFR), 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 209)
- Oil, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 210)
- Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 211)
- U.S. Life Lines, Department of Navy Publication, 1971, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 212)
- Secretary Kissinger Discussion Items, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 213)
- Secretary Kissinger Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 214)
- Secretary Kissinger Press Conferences and Speeches, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 215)
- Secretary Kissinger Press Conferences and Speeches, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 215.1)
- Conference on Security and Cooperation in Europe (CSCE), 1975 (Box 8, Folder 216)
- Detente, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 217)
- Law of the Sea, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 218)
- Threshold Nuclear Test Ban Treaty, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 219)
- Raw Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 220)
- East-West Economics, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 221)
- International Food, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 222)
- Public Opinion Polls, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 223)
- Terrorism, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 224)
- Trade, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 225)
- Multinational Corporations, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 226)
- United Nations, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 227)
- Foreign Investment in the United States, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 228)
- Speeches by Heads of State and Dignitaries, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 229)
- Foreign Concerns About U.S. Policy, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 230)
- Foreign Comments on the U.S. Election, November 1976 (Box 9, Folder 231)
- Angola, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 232)
- Foreign Relations/Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 233)
- White House Fellows Foreign Trips, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 234)
- Africa, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 235)
- Asia, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 236)
- Federal Republic of Germany, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 237)
- Japan, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 238)
- Greece and Turkey, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 239)
- Greenland, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 240)
- Iran, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 241)
- Israel, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 242)
- Italy, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 243)
- Italy, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 243.1)
- Malaysia, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 244)
- Latin America, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 245)
- Pakistan, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 246)
- New Zealand, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 247)
- Middle East, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 248)
- Korea, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 249)
- U.S. Strategy in Asia, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 250)
- Bali, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 251)
- Bali, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 251.1)
- Canada, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 252)
- Australia, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 253)
- Cambodia Crisis - "Mayaguez", 1975 (Box 9, Folder 254)
- Caribbean, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 255)
- People's Republic of China, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 256)
- Cyprus, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 257)
- France, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 258)
- Panama, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 259)
- Spain, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 260)
- Lebanon, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 261)
- Southeast Asia - Viet Name and Other Countries, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 262)
- Southeast Asia - Cambodia, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 262.1)
- Saudi Arabia, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 263)
- Portugal, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 264)
- Critical Materials/Strategic Stockpile, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 265)
- President William Tolbert of Liberia, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 266)
- Singapore, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 267)
- Contact with Communist Officials, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 268)
- Energy, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 269)
- Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 270)
- DC Metro Subway Construction and Financing, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 271)
- President Ford's Speeches, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 272)
- Science, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 273)
- Steel, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 274)
- Personnel - General, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 275)
- Frances Knight - Passport Office, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 276)
- Carleton Smith - Assistant to J. Paul Getty, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 277)
- Soviet Union, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 278)
- Soviet Union, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 279)
- Soviet Union, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 280)
- Soviet Statements, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 281)
- Tunisia, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 282)
- Western Europe, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 283)
- Yugoslavia, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 284)
- Martim L. Cabral, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 285)
- Enzo de Chiara - Cousin of President Leone of Italy, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 286)
- Enzo de Chiara - Cousin of President Leone of Italy, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 286.1)
- Queen Elizabeth II's State Visit, July 6-11, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 287)
- President Giscard d'Estaing's Visit to Yorktown, Virginia, May 1976 (Box 10, Folder 288)
- Lord Mountbatten, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 289)
- Meetings with Congressional Leaders, January-September 1975 (Box 11, Folder 290)
- Meetings with Congressional Leaders, October 1975-June 1976 (Box 11, Folder 290.1)
- Vice Presidential Travel, Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 291)
- Vice Presidential Travel, Miscellaneous, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 291.1)
- Input for Report to the President, January 1976 (Box 11, Folder 292)
- NAR Remarks on the Soviet Union, May 1976 (Box 11, Folder 293)
- International Naval Review and Operation Sail, July 1976 (Box 11, Folder 294)
- International Naval Review and Operation Sail, july 1976 (Box 11, Folder 294.1)
- Vice Presidential Correspondence, January 1977 (Box 11, Folder 295)
- Vice Presidential Correspondence, September-December 1976 (Box 11, Folder 296)
- Vice Presidential Correspondence, May-August 1976 (Box 11, Folder 296.1)
- Vice Presidential Correspondence, January-April 1976 (Box 11, Folder 296.2)
- Vice Presidential Correspondence, July-December 1975 (Box 11, Folder 297)
- Vice Presidential Correspondence, January-June 1975 (Box 11, Folder 297.1)
- NAR on Freedom of the Seas Speech Draft, March 1976 (Box 11, Folder 298)
- Staff Organization, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 299)
- NAR Speech Drafts, February-September 1975 (Box 11, Folder 300)
- NAR Speech Drafts, November 1975, January 1976 (Box 11, Folder 300.1)
- Q&A Following Speech by NAR to National Defense University, December 9, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 300.2)
- "Donovan and the CIA: A History," Volume 1 (Box 11, Folder 301)
- "Donovan and the CIA: A History," Volume 2 (Box 11, Folder 302)
- State Department's Consumer Conference, October 1976 (Box 11, Folder 303)
- Drafts for Republican Platform, 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 304)
- Drafts for Republican Platform, 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 11, Folder 304.1)
- CLOSED FOLDER (Box 11, Folder 305)
- CLOSED FOLDER (Box 12, Folder 306)
- Event for Wives of Japanese Dignitaries, Hosted by Mrs. Rockefeller, July-August 1975 (Box 12, Folder 307)
- CLOSED FOLDER (Box 12, Folder 308)
- CLOSED FOLDER (Box 12, Folder 309)
- Vice Presidential Flag and Seal, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 310)
- Vice President's Official Residence, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 311)
- Emergency Procedures Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 312)
- Emergency Procedures Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 312.1)
- Service Academy Program, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 313)
- Service Academy Program, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 313.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, January 1977 (Box 12, Folder 314)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, September 1976 (Box 12, Folder 315)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, October 1976 (Box 12, Folder 315.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 315), September 1976 (Box 12, Folder 315.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, November 1976 (Box 12, Folder 316)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, December 1976 (Box 12, Folder 316.1)
- Operations Coordinating Board and Psychological Warfare, 1953-1955; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 317)
- Operations Coordinating Board and Psychological Warfare, 1953-1955; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 317.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, May 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 318)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, May 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 318.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, June 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 318.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, June 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 12, Folder 318.3)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, July 1976 (Box 12, Folder 319)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, August 1976 (Box 12, Folder 319.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, July-August 1976 (Box 12, Folder 319.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 319), July 1976 (Box 12, Folder 319.3)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, March 1976 (Box 12, Folder 320)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, April 1976 (Box 12, Folder 320.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, March-April 1976 (Box 12, Folder 320.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 320), March 1976 (Box 12, Folder 320.3)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 320.1), April 1976 (Box 12, Folder 320.4)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 320.2), March-April 1976 (Box 12, Folder 320.5)
- Report - "Japan: Making Foreign Economic Policy", c. 1976 (Box 12, Folder 321)
- Statement by the Director of Central Intelligence to the Commission on CIA Activities Within the United States, January 13, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 322)
- Report to the President on Organization and Management of the Foreign Intelligence Community, December 16, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 323)
- Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 324)
- CIA Commission - General, January 1975 (Box 13, Folder 325)
- CIA Policy and Legal Matters, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 326)
- CIA Commission - NAR's Handwritten Notes, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 327)
- Security of U.S. Telecommunications, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 328)
- Summary and Analysis of Colby Report, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 329)
- CIA Commission Chron File, January 1975 (Box 13, Folder 330)
- CIA Commission Chron File, February-March 1975 (Box 13, Folder 330.1)
- CIA Commission Chron File, April 1975 (Box 13, Folder 330.2)
- CIA News Clippings, January-February 1975 (Box 13, Folder 331)
- CIA News Clippings, March 1975 (Box 13, Folder 331.1)
- CIA News Clippings, April 1975 (Box 13, Folder 331.2)
- CIA News Clippings, May-June 1975 (Box 13, Folder 331.3)
- CIA Commission Chron File, May 1975 (Box 13, Folder 332)
- CIA Commission Chron File, June 1975 (Box 13, Folder 332.1)
- CIA Commission Chron File, July-August 1975 (Box 13, Folder 332.2)
- CIA Commission Chron File, Unsorted, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 332.3)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, January-February 1976 (Box 13, Folder 333)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, February 1976 (Box 13, Folder 333.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, January 1976 (Box 13, Folder 333.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 333.1), February 1976 (Box 13, Folder 333.3)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, November-December 1975 (Box 13, Folder 334)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, December 1975 (Box 13, Folder 334.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, November 1975 (Box 13, Folder 334.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 334.2), November 1975 (Box 13, Folder 334.3)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, August 1975 (Box 14, Folder 335)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, July 1975 (Box 14, Folder 335.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 335.1), July 1975 (Box 14, Folder 335.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, Unsorted, September-October 1975 (Box 14, Folder 336)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, October 1975 (Box 14, Folder 336.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, September 1975 (Box 14, Folder 336.2)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 336.1), October 1975 (Box 14, Folder 336.3)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 336.2), September 1975 (Box 14, Folder 336.4)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, June 1975 (Box 14, Folder 337)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, May 1975 (Box 14, Folder 337.1)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File (from Folder 337), June 1975 (Box 14, Folder 337.2)
- Report - "American Intelligence: A Framework for the Future", October 13, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 338)
- Report - "American Intelligence: A Framework for the Future" - Annexes, October 13, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 338.1)
- Operations Coordinating Board #4, 1955, 1974; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 339)
- Operations Coordinating Board #4, 1955, 1974; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 339.1)
- Capt. John Howe's Chron File, March/April 1975 (Box 14, Folder 340)
- Capt. John Howe's Chron File, April 1975 (Box 14, Folder 340.1)
- Capt. John Howe's Chron File, March 1975 (Box 14, Folder 340.2)
- Operations Coordinating Board #2, 1955, 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 341)
- Operations Coordinating Board #2, 1955, 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 341.1)
- Operations Coordinating Board #3, 1955; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 342)
- Operations Coordinating Board #3, 1955; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 342.1)
- Pre-Vice Presidential Period - Briefing Material, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 343)
- Capt. Jon Howe's Chron File, January-February 1975 (Box 14, Folder 344)
- President's Foreign Intelligence Advisory Board (PFIAB), June 1975 (Box 15, Folder 345)
- CIA Commission Personnel Matters, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 346)
- CIA Commission Meeting Agenda and Attendees, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 347)
- CIA Commission General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 348)
- CIA Commission Administrative Details, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 349)
- Memo to President Ford from Donald Rumsfeld on CIA Director Position, June 15, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 350)
- CIA Commission Staff Photograph, July 2, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 351)
- CIA Commission Report, 1975
  - NAR Drafts of Chapters, April 1975 (Box 15, Folder 352)
  - NAR Drafts of Chapters, May 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 353)
  - NAR Drafts of Chapters, May 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 15, Folder 353.1)
  - Part I, Summary of Investigation, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 354)
  - Part II, Chapters 4-6, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 355)
  - Part III, Chapters 7-8, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 356)
  - Part IV, Chapter 9, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 357)
  - Chapter 10, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 358)
  - Chapter 11, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 359)
  - Chapter 12, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 360)
  - Chapter 13, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 361)
  - Chapter 14, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 362)
  - Chapter 15 Notes and Chapter 16, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 363)
  - Chapter 17, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 364)
  - Chapter 18, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 365)
  - Chapter 19, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 366)
  - Appendices I-VI, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 367)
  - Appendix VII, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 368)
- Report of Chief of Central Intelligence Staff, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 369)
- CIA/Office of Economic Research Intelligence Reports for Special Representative for Trade Negotiations, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 370)
- CLOSED FOLDER (Box 15, Folder 371)
- Ann Whitman's CIA Commission File, January-June 1975 (Box 15, Folder 372)
- Issues for the Intelligence Community, ca. 1976 (Box 15, Folder 373)
- Civil Defense, November 1976-January 1977 (Box 15, Folder 374)
- Report - Psychological Aspects of U.S. Strategy, November 1955; 2 volumes (Box 15, Folder 375)
- Report of the Quantico Vulnerabilities Panel, June 1955 (Box 15, Folder 376)
- White House Press Releases on Intelligence, February 1976 (Box 16, Folder 377)
- Operations Coordinating Board #6, 1955; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 378)
- Operations Coordinating Board #6, 1955; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 378.1)
- Operations Coordinating Board #5, 1955; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 16, Folder 379)
- Operations Coordinating Board #5, 1955; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 16, Folder 379.1)
- Operations Coordinating Board #5, 1955; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 16, Folder 379.2)
- Report - "Worldwide Communist Propaganda Activities in 1954", February 1955; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 380)
- Report - "Worldwide Communist Propaganda Activities in 1954", February 1955; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 380.1)
- Jurisdiction of the CIA Commission - Sections A-E, May 1, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 381)
- Jurisdiction of the CIA Commission - Sections F-J, May 1, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 381.1)
- Memo to NAR on CIA Commission Report Problems, With Staff Annotations, May 15, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 382)
- CIA Commission Current (possibly Peter Wallison files), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 383)
- CIA Commission Current (possibly Peter Wallison files), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 383.1)
- CIA Commission Current - Executive Order Drafts, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 383.2)
- CIA Commission Follow-up (possibly Peter Wallison files), May-July 1975 (Box 16, Folder 384)
- CIA Commission Follow-up (possibly Peter Wallison files), August-December 1975 (Box 16, Folder 384.1)
- CIA Commission Follow-up (possibly Peter Wallison files), January-June 1975 (Box 16, Folder 384.2)
- CIA Commission Report Book IV - Memo on Restructuring of Intelligence Community, October 15, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 385)
- Decision Book for the President on the Intelligence Community, December 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 386)
- Decision Book for the President on the Intelligence Community, December 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 387)
- CIA Commission Report Book I - NAR Binder, January-June 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 388)
- CIA Commission Report Book I - NAR Binder, January-June 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 388.1)
- CIA Commission Report Book II - NAR Binder, January-June 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 389)
- CIA Commission Report Book II - NAR Binder, January-June 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 389.1)
- CIA Commission Report Book III - NAR Binder, January-August 1975; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 390)
- CIA Commission Report Book III - NAR Binder, January-August 1975; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 390.1)
- CIA Commission Report Book IV - NAR Binder, August 1975-March 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 391)
- CIA Commission Report Book IV - NAR Binder, August 1975-March 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 17, Folder 391.1)
- CIA Commission - Vice President's Annex, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 392)
- Murphy Commission Background Volumes, 1973-1975
  - Book I, compiled February 7, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 393)
    Status of Committee work and plans for next Commission meeting. Summaries of issues.
    Tab A - Committee Membership Tab B - Congressional Issues Tab C - Intelligence and National Security (Rockefeller Reports) Tab D - International Economics Tab E - Public Diplomacy Tab F - Selected Minutes of Commission Meetings Tab G - The Constitution
  - Book II, compiled February 13, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 394)
    Status of Committee deliberations, plans for Commission meetings, and work on Vice Presidential requests.
    Tab A - Summary of National Security Issues Tab B - Latin America Report Tab C - West Coast Hearings Tab D - Eisenhower Book Tab E - Drucker's "Fortune" Article Tab F - DOD Studies
  - Book III, compiled February 17, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 395)
    Draft of report of the National Security Committee.
    Tab A - Criticisms of NSC Management Tab B - Unsubstantiated Statements Tab C - Recommendations TAb D - First Draft - National Security Committee Report
  - Book IV, compiled February 20, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 396)
    Allison Report on National Security Cases.
    Tab A - Defense and Arms Control Cases Tab B - Examples of Questionable Case Analysis and Statements Tab C - Failures to Attend to the Longer Run Tab D - Disadvantages of the "1969" NSC System Tab E - Costs of "Closed" System Tab F - Selected References to Secretary Kissinger Tab G - Specific Findings and Recommendations from Summary Volumes Tab H - Allison Memorandum to Subcommittee on National Security
  - Book V, compiled February 21, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 397)
    Update of Commission developments for week covering Committee progress, project status, possible action, plans for Commissioners meeting, and background materials.
    Tab A - Effect of Recently Enacted Legislative Restrictions on Executive Foreign Affairs Authority Tab B - 1974 Foreign Assistance Act Tab C - Remarks of the President at the Salute to the Vice President Dinner (Feb. 13, 1975) Tab D - Commission "Global Issues" Research Project
  - Book VI, compiled March 3, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 398)
    Briefing book of Vice President's first meeting as a Commissioner. Progress reports on commission work. Testimony of Secretary Kissinger.
    Tab A - Comments on Mansfield Trip to China Tab B - Engelhard Report on China Trip Tab C - Committee Progress Reports Tab D - Federal Advisory Committee Act Tab E - Questions for Secretary Kissinger Tab F - Commission Members Tab G - Talking Points on Impact of Restrictive Legislation Tab H - Effects of Recent Legislative Restrictions (Includes Restrictive Provisions of Foreign Assistance Act) Tab I - Non-interference in International Affairs Tab J - Secretary Kissinger's Remarks on Relations with Congress Tab K - Casey Testimony on International Policy Tab L - State Department Submission to Murphy Commission
  - Book VII, compiled March 7, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 399)
    Report on Committee progress, plans for March 17 meeting, and background materials on developing issues.
    Tab A - Recommendations Tab B - Report of National Security Committee Meeting Tab C - Study of U.S. Foreign Economic Policy Making Tab D - War Powers, Executive Agreements and Executive Privilege Tab E - Executive Branch Consultations with Congress on Military Assistance to Turkey Tab F - Index of Commission Testimony
  - Book VIII, compiled March 17, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 400)